friendquestions.com 2014-06-20

# FQ Privacy Policy Original

FRIEND QUESTIONS PRIVACY POLICY

October 2009

FriendQuestions.com (“the Website”) is a website created and operated by Onoko Limited (“the Company”, or “us” or “we”), a limited liability company registered in Hong Kong.

This privacy policy sets out how we use and protect any information that you give us when you use the Website.

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should you provide us with information by which you can be identified (“Personal Information”) when using the Website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

The Company may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1 October 2009.

  1. PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT:

  1. Personal Information retrieved from Facebook

When you first access the Website, you will be redirected to a Facebook Application Authorization Screen, where you will be invited to grant us access to your personal information. If you grant access, Facebook may provide us with the following information which we will store and use in accordance with law:

  1. Your Facebook unique identifier number (UID)
  2. Your full name
  3. The educational, regional, and workplace networks you belong to
  4. Your work and education history
  5. Your current location (city and country)
  6. Your hometown location (city and country)
  7. Your language preference
  8. Your date of birth
  9. Your gender
  10. The names and UIDs of your Facebook friends
  11. Your relationship status
  12. Facebook Pages that you are a “fan” of
  13. Facebook Groups that you are a member of
  14. Facebook Photos that you shared or are tagged in.
  15. Your activities and interests
  16. Other Facebook profile information made available to us by Facebook

  2. Other Personal Information obtained through use of the Website

In addition, we may collect and store the following information:

  1. Your IP address
  2. The pages you visit
  3. Content you create through the website
  4. Activity you undertake while using the website (e.g. what links you click on)

 2\. WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

The information we collect about you is used to deliver and improve our products and services, and in particular (but not exclusively) for the following purposes:

  1. To personalize Website content:

We may use your Personal Information to personalize content when you access the website. For example, we may generate a list of questions based on the names and genders of your friends.

  2. To send you targeted email marketing and notifications

We may periodically send you emails about:

  1. New content on the Website that may be of interest to you.
  2. User activity on the Website.
  3. Support information related to inquiries or issues you have on the Website.
  4. Information about offers, content, products and services created by us or third parties that we think may be of interest to you.
  5. Market research surveys on behalf of ourselves or third parties.
  6. Other information created by ourselves or third parties that we think may be of interest to you.

Any emails we send you will contain opt-out/unsubscribe information. You can adjust your email preferences at any time by clicking on a link in the email, or by sending a reply message.

Any emails we send you on behalf of partner third parties will be sent by us. We will not pass personally identifiable information about you (e.g. your name, Facebook ID, or email address) to partner third parties, except in accordance with clause 3(b). We may, however, provide third parties with aggregated, anonymized information for marketing purposes (e.g. the number of female users in London who are fans of Chocolate).

c.        To send you targeted information via non-email communication channels

We may send you versions of the information listed in section 2b(i-vi) via non-email communication channels, including but not limited to Facebook Fan Page updates, phone notifications, and Facebook notifications. You can unsubscribe from these communications at any time using the built-in feature appropriate to the channel (e.g. unsubscribing from our Facebook Pages, or removing the application).

d.         Internal Record Keeping

Your use and behavior on the Website or in response to our communications may be stored and analyzed on an individual or aggregate basis to help us improve our products or services, investigate problems, and to comply with any legal requirements imposed upon us.

e.        Targeted Advertising

The Website is financially supported by advertising. Your personal information may be used to target advertising of interest to you. We will not pass personally identifiable information about you (e.g. your name, Facebook ID, or email address) to advertising third parties, except in accordance with clause 3(b). We may, however, provide third parties with aggregated, anonymized information for marketing purposes (e.g. the number of female users in London who are a fan of Chocolate).

3\. PROTECTING YOUR DATA

 a. Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

b. Transfer of Personal Information to Third Parties

We may deliver advertising or send you promotional information on behalf of third parties, but we will not transfer personally identifiable information about you (e.g. your name, Facebook UID or email address) to a third party except:

  1. To technology providers used in the delivery of the Website and/or the delivery of communication to you, who must agree to keep your information confidential, and to use your information only for the technical purpose agreed.
  2. To other companies majority owned or operated by the Company.
  3. To an acquiring company in the event that the Website or Company are sold by their current owners. In the event of such an acquisition, your personal information will be transferred to the new owner.
  4. To other third parties (e.g. potential investors, advertisers) on an aggregated, anonymized basis for marketing purposes (e.g. the number of female users in London who are a fan of Chocolate).
  5. Otherwise as required by law.

4\. OTHER ISSUES

 a.         Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. We do not directly place any cookies on your computer, but we use the following third party services which may place cookies on your computer, or monitor your activity on the website:

i. Google Analytics \- Google may place traffic log cookies to identify which Website functions are being used. This helps us analyse data about web traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes. Data is anonymized and held indefinitely.

ii. Facebook Authentication \- When you visit the Website, Facebook may place an authentication cookie on your computer which allows you to use the Website without repeatedly signing in (“Single Sign On”), and to send authenticated information to and from Facebook.

  1. Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

5\. CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

a. Requesting information held about you

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to the address listed below. Please ensure that you include your name and Facebook UID or email address so that we can identify you.

b. Deleting information held about you

You may request that we delete all personal information held about you. No fee will be payable. If you would like us to do this, please write to the address listed below. Please ensure that you include your name and Facebook UID or email address so that we can identify you.

  2.  Correcting information held about you

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the address listed below. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

COMMUNICATING WITH US:

Please send any communications related to privacy to:

Mr. Janakan Arulkumarasan

janakan.arulkumarasan@onoko.com

Onoko Limited

16B, Block 4, Tolo Place

628 Sai Sha Road

Ma On Shan, NT

Hong Kong
